targetly.com 2015-05-18

# Privacy - Targetly

Effective Date: 03/17/2014 What Do You Do With My Information?

At Targetly, LLC("Targetly"), we respect your privacy and take protecting it seriously. This Privacy Policy covers our collection, use and disclosure of information we collect through our website and service www.Targetly.com. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged Targetly.

Here's what we do - and, more importantly, don't do - with any information you provide us.

### "I Am An Targetly Affiliate."

Your name, address, phone and fax number, email address, tax ID number or SSN and any other information you provide are held in strict confidence. We collect this information only so we can generate your commission checks and so we can meet United States federal tax requirements.

We do not sell or share your information with anyone else.

### "I Am A Subscriber To An Email List Managed Using Targetly."

Your email address, name and any other information you provide such as address and phone number you provide to our customers are held in strict confidence. We only keep your information so that the customer whose email list you signed up to can email you.

We do not contact you. We do not sell or share your information with anyone else.

Targetly collects information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. Targetly works with its Clients to help them provide notice to their customers concerning, the purpose for which personal information is collected.

We collect information for our clients, if you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the client that you interact with directly.If you are a Client and would like to update your account please contact us at the contact information listed below

Targetly has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to the Targetly's Client (the data controller). If the Client requests Targetly to remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 business days.

Targetly may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the provisions in this Policy regarding notice and choice and the service agreements with our Clients.

Targetly will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed provide services to our Client. Targetly will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Newsletters

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters you may follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in each of the communications you receive.

#### What About Clear Gifs?

We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers' personal information.

We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.

### "I Am An Targetly Customer."

Your account information is held in strict confidence. All customers' account information is.

We do not sell or share your information with anyone. We only collect information like your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and billing information so we can provide the email marketing services described on this website.

### Service Providers

We use third party software and partners to perform services on our behalf. These services include credit card processing, fraud protection, marketing, analytics, etc. When you sign up for Targetly we will share only the personal information necessary for these services to perform their functions.

### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

In the event Targetly goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personal information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

#### Access To Personal Information

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at help@Targetly.com. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

#### Security

The security of your personal information and our clients' information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as login credentials and credit card information) we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us.

#### What About Cookies?

We do use cookies to track a number of activities and provide a desirable experience for our affiliates, our customers, and their subscribers. We do link the information we store in cookies to any personal information you submit while on our site.

We treat any data that we collect with a cookie with the same high respect that we treat other data about customers, subscribers and affiliates, and only use it in ways that are consistent with the policies described above.

In addition to our own cookies, our third party advertisers may use them to both improve the performance of our service and provide features such as advertising. You can restrict the use of cookies or delete them from your browser at anytime by configuring your browser settings. (Please note that restricting cookies can interfere with some of the functionality of our website.)

#### What About Web beacons?

Our third party partners employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), images, and scripts that help them better manage content on our site. We [do/do not] tie the information gathered to our Customers’ or Users’ personal information.

#### What About Flash LSOs?

We use local shared objects, also known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences such as volume control or high game score, or display content based upon what you view on our site to personalize your visit. Third Parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity, use Flash cookies to collect and store information. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored.Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies.To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies click here.

#### What About Log Files?

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

#### Advertising

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personal information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking here. Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

#### Notification Of Privacy Policy Changes

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at via email at support@targetly.com or via postal mail at 4905 NE Cully Blvd, Portland, OR 97218, USA
